recenttips.com 2015-06-12

# Privacy Policy | Recent Tips

**Privacy Policy for www.RECENTTIPS.com**  
By using our Services you Agree to our Terms of Service, if You Don’t accept These Terms then Pls Leave the site.

The contents are Provided to users for informational purposes only and as a user you agree that **www.RECENTTIPS.com** Team is not responsible for your experience with These Contents.  
**www.RECENTTIPS.com** is Not Responsible for any loss or Damage occurred due to use of the Contents or Services Provided by Us.  
**www.RECENTTIPS.com** is a Open Public service site and its Owners can’t be Held Responsible for any Activities of its Users.  
**www.RECENTTIPS.com** Users are Not allowed to Spam Our Contact emails, You Should be Polite and Up To the Point When you are Looking to Contact Us.  
**www.RECENTTIPS.com** We Respect The Real Content Owners, If Your Content is added in our site (Real Owners only) and you want it to be removed, Please contact us and we will remove it immediately after Receiving Your Mail.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our  
privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at  
ramzukhan@gmail.com  
At **www.RECENTTIPS.com** , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme  
importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of  
personal information is received and collected by  
**www.RECENTTIPS.com** and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, **www.RECENTTIPS.com** makes use of log  
files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (  
IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ),  
date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to  
analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around  
the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and  
other such information are not linked to any information that is  
personally identifiable.  
Cookies and Web Beacons  
**www.RECENTTIPS.com** does not use cookies.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google or any other third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads  
on **www.RECENTTIPS.com**.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users  
based on their visit to **www.RECENTTIPS.com** and other sites on the  
Internet.  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons  
on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
Adhitz  
infolinks  
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the  
advertisements and links that appear on **www.RECENTTIPS.com** send  
directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP  
address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies,  
JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party  
ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements  
and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  
**www.RECENTTIPS.com** has no access to or control over these  
cookies that are used by third-party advertisers  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third –  
party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as  
well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.  
**www.RECENTTIPS.com** ’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we  
cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual  
browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
